diskdoctors.com 2015-05-12

# Disk Doctors.com

**Private Identification Info**

We used to collect personal information from various users in different ways like when user places an order, visits our page, fills a form and other activities in which we find them available on our website. Users are asked for their email addresses, phone numbers and appropriate names. Anyway, user may also use our page as anonymous. We usually collect information from visitors only if they want to give their information to us. 

**Non-personal Recognition Info**

We collect non-personal recognition info of users when they come to connect our website. Non-personal recognition info contains the type of computer, browser name and a number of technical information which include internet service providers, operating system and other information etc. 

**Internet Browser Cookies**

To increase user experience we have included cookies in our website. To keep the record saved on user's hard drive, cookies are saved on user's computer, which is sometimes used to track info about them. User may change his browser's settings to refuse cookies; after all, his browser will be able to alert him when cookies are being sent. 

**How we Use Collected Information**

Disk Doctors Labs Inc. acquires user private information for these reasons. 

  * To enhance customer support 

Details you supply allow us to respond to your customer support requests and support needs more effectively. 

  * To enhance web site 

The feedback you provide can help us to improve our services and products. 

  * To deliver periodic email messages

The email address is used to send updates and other user information regarding their order. However, it may also be used to give them feedback for their questions, requests and inquiries. If user subscribes to our mailing list, he/she will get emails that will contain company updates, news or service information etc. If user doesn't want to receive emails from us, he/she will be unsubscribed from receiving emails; they can accomplish this after they visit our website. 

**The Way we Secure your Details**

We know various ways to keep the data secured, since we adopt different data collection, data processing practices like to secure your data against alteration, unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction of your personal information like username, password and the transaction information. 

**Sharing Your Own Info**

We do not sell and disclose user's personal information to other people. 

**Variations to the Current Privacy Policy**

Disk Doctors Labs Inc. has the discretion to modify the privacy policy at any time we want. Whenever we do, we will mention the updated date on the bottom of the page. We motivate the users to regularly check the page to remain aware of any changes about how we use to protect the client information that we collect. You accept and agree that, it is your responsibility to check this privacy policy regularly and keep yourself aware of the changes. 

**Your Acceptance for these Conditions**

After using this website you accept this policy. In case you are not agreed to the policy, you are requested to not use our website. If you use the website further, your acceptance will be considered for those changes.
